xpmedia.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy - XPMedia.com

Last updated May 23, 2018

## REVISIONS

XPMEDIA.COM INC. MAY REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE ONLINE TERMS OF USE AND ANY OTHER POLICIES AND AGREEMENTS AT ANY TIME BY UPDATING THIS POSTING. YOU SHOULD VISIT THIS PAGE FROM TIME TO TIME TO REVIEW THE THEN CURRENT TERMS BECAUSE THEY ARE BINDING ON YOU. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE AFTER SUCH CHANGES ARE IMPLEMENTED CONSTITUTES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THESE CHANGES.  CERTAIN PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS MAY BE SUPERSEDED BY EXPRESSLY DESIGNATED TERMS LOCATED ON PARTICULAR PAGES OF THIS WEBSITE.

Our Privacy Policy covers XPmedia.com Inc and its website:

XPmedia.com's website can be accessed at [www.xpmedia.com](http://www.xpmedia.com/).  By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by XPmedia.com as set forth in the Privacy Policy currently in effect. If we decide to change our policy, such changes will be posted here on the website. Please check back periodically to ensure that you have read the most current policy. 

## Location of Data

XPMedia is based in the United States. We provide services globally using computer systems, servers, and databases located in the U.S. When you use our services from outside of the U.S., your information will therefore be transferred to, stored in, and processed in the U.S. Data is collected, stored, used, and shared as set forth in our privacy policies.

## European Users

The European Commission has determined that the transfer of personal information of its residents outside of Europe must be subject to a legal framework that adequately protects it. We transfer personal information of European Economic Area ("EEA") and Swiss residents to the U.S. (or elsewhere) based upon the following legal frameworks:

  * Legitimate business interests: We could not provide our services or comply with our obligations to you without transferring your personal information to the U.S.
  * Consent: We may transfer your personal information when we receive your express, revocable consent.
  * Our use of Standard Contractual Clauses (also known as “Model Clauses”) where appropriate.

## GDPR

We comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Law ("GDPR"), which governs the protection of personal data of EU residents. To find out more about GDPR, please visit the European Union’s website, at https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en.

EU users have the rights to: opt out of cookies; access, correct, delete, restrict or object to our use of their personal information; be forgotten; and data portability. We enable exercise of these rights through our products (which we reserve the right to modify). For example, we allow users to change their information, download their videos, and close their accounts. We also fulfil our obligations in response to direct requests.

If you require assistance, please contact our Data Protection Officer. We may require additional information from you to fulfil your requests. We may charge a reasonable fee if your request imposes an unreasonable cost on us.

We will afford UK-based users with all rights available to EU users, regardless of the UK’s EU member status.

## Controllers and Processors

Some laws, including the GDPR, differentiate between controllers and processors of data. A "controller" has a direct relationship with you and exercises control over the use of your data. The third-party vendors that help a controller provide a service are considered "processors" because they process the controller’s customer data at the controller’s request (examples are payment processors and cloud-based hosting providers).

All XPMedia entities are controllers of personal information on users who upload and live stream videos.

With respect to the XPMedia platform, XPMedia Inc. are controllers of personal data of end users who view uploaders’ videos or live streams as these XPMedia entities have direct relationships with the end user viewers.

## Dispute Resolution

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint. We encourage you to begin by contacting our Data Protection Officer. We endeavor to respond to requests promptly.

EU residents have the right to lodge complaints with the data protection authority of their country of residence.

## Data Protection Officer

For any questions, inquiries, or complaints, please contact us at:

General Counsel and Data Protection Officer

XPMedia Inc.

PO Box 1017

Maricopa, AZ 85139

## ANONYMOUS ACCESS TO VISITORS

You can access XPmedia.com's website home page and browse our site without

disclosing your personal data.

## SERVICES AND LINKS OF OUR WEBSITE

Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. Our website includes links to other web service sites. Please note that these third party web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors who connect to their links. These websites are owned and operated independently of XPmedia.com and have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. Any information that you provide to these websites will be governed under the terms of their respective privacy policies, if any. XPmedia.com has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of these third party websites and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these websites. XPmedia.com’s Pivacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by [www.XPmedia.com](http://www.xpmedia.com/).

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION; PURPOSE AND USE

XPmedia.com collects personally-identifiable information when you voluntarily fill out the forms on this website to request assistance, literature or information, or to submit an application to become an Affiliate, or to place a product order or a subscription request. We retain that information in our database and use it to fulfill your request as well as using it for technical administration of the website, research and development, customer administration, and marketing. We do not require this information for users to obtain access to any part of our public website.

XPmedia.com keeps track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We use “cookies” and other Web technologies to collect information and support certain features and functionality of our website. We may collect information about the ways you use [www.xpmedia.com](http://www.xpmedia.com/), such as which pages you visit, which links you use, and how long you stay on each page. We may track the items in your shopping cart. We may also keep track of how you got to [www.xpmedia.com](http://www.xpmedia.com/) and any links you click on to leave [www.xpmedia.com](http://www.xpmedia.com/).

XPmedia.com does not link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about any specific individual. XPmedia.com collects only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not seek or collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or public agencies or private organizations.

By sending XPmedia.com an electronic mail message (for example, an e-mail message containing an information request), you may be sending us personally-identifiable information. In these cases, we may retain the information as long as necessary to respond to your request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail.

Before collecting personally-identifiable information for new purposes, we will prominently disclose:

• why we are requesting the information;

• how it will be used;

• how long it may be retained; and

• under what conditions, and with whom, it may be shared.

If we wish to use your personal data for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes by indicating in a box at the point on the website where personal data is collected.

## ONLINE ORDERING

XPmedia.com takes careful measures to protect your ordering and credit card information and to prevent the loss and misuse of such information. When you submit an order to XPmedia.com on this website, your information is encrypted and stored behind a firewall. You can purchase products and services or register to receive materials and information. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number and credit/debit card information. XPmedia.com uses the personal information you provide only to process that order. XPmedia.com does not share the information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. XPmedia.com’s credit/debit card and order processing is protected by Digicert.

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY 

XPmedia.com's marketing efforts are directed principally to adults and therefore this website is intended for use by those 13 years or older only. No information should be submitted to or posted on this website by visitors under the age of 13. Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and all other applicable laws. This website is intended for use by those 13 years or older.

YOU MUST BE THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER THIRTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEBSITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEBSITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO

XPmedia.com does not disclose your personal data to any affiliated company(ies) or other organizations.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS UNDER THE CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT AND THE CALIFORNIA BUSINESS AND PROFESSIONS CODE 

This Privacy Policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that XPmedia.com collects through this commercial website and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom XPmedia.com may share that personally identifiable information. 

XPmedia.com maintains a process for an individual consumer who uses or visits our commercial website or online service to review and request changes to any of his or her personally identifiable information that is collected through our website. See the section below entitled “ACCESS TO THE PERSONAL DATA HELD BY XPMEDIA.COM”.

The section entitled "REVISIONS" above describes the process by which XPmedia.com  notifies consumers who use or visit our commercial website or online service of material changes to our company's Privacy Policy for this website or online service.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is listed at the beginning of this Privacy Policy under the heading, "Last updated."

For the purposes of this policy and California compliance the following definitions apply:

Depending on the visitor's activity in our commercial website or online service, the following "personally identifiable information" may be collected, in addition to information set forth in other sections of this Privacy Policy.

The term "personally identifiable information" means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by XPmedia.com from an individual and maintained by XPmedia.com in an accessible form, and may include any of the following:

  * A first and last name.
  * A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town.
  * An e-mail address.
  * A telephone number. .
  * Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual.
  * Information concerning a user that this website or online service collects online, from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combination with an identifier described within this privacy policy.

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, if any, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to sross@xpmedia.com and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the domain name of the website you are inquiring about, along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request. 

## CONFIDENTIALITY / SECURITY 

XPmedia.com provides a secure transmission method to send identifiers (including but not limited to credit card details, website password and so forth). Our website provides forms allowing visitors to submit search engine queries, questionnaires, feedback, or other information. Some of these forms may request personally-identifiable information (e.g., name, address, e-mail address) for specific purposes, such as when the submitter is requesting a personal response, registering for a subscription, submitting an Affiliate application or subscribing to a mailing list.

We may store non-personally-identifiable information we collect (such as search engine queries and anonymous survey responses) indefinitely to help us better understand and meet the needs of our visitors. This information is neither made available to any third parties nor combined with any other information at our disposal. XPmedia.com has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

All XPmedia.com employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to governmental institutions and authorities unless required by court order, by law, or by federal, state or municipal regulation. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

## OFFICIAL LANGUAGE

The official language of this website, Privacy Policy and all documents provided on this website is American English. Regardless of whether this website or any of the documents provided on this website is translated into one or more other languages for marketing purposes or any other purpose, the official language is and shall remain American English. The American English form of this website and all documents provided on this website shall control and determine the interpretation thereof.

## ACCESS TO THE PERSONAL DATA HELD BY XPMEDIA.COM

You can ask XPmedia.com whether we are keeping personal data about you by sending an email to user@xpmedia.com. Upon request, XPmedia.com will provide you with a readable copy of your personal data held by us, if any such information exists, within a week. XPmedia.com reserves the right to require proof of your identity before providing any requested information. Upon proof of identification satisfactory to XPmedia.com, we will provide the information without charge.  

XPmedia.com allows you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased from XPmedia.com's database.

## PRIVACY COMPLIANCE

It is XPmedia.com’s policy to follow the Principles for Providing and Using Personal Information ("Privacy Principles"), published by the Information Infrastructure Task Force on June 6, 1995, and the International Chamber of Commerce (ICC) Guidelines on advertising and Marketing on the Internet.

## PRIVACY SUPPORT

If you have an inquiry or concern about this Privacy Policy, please contact sross@xpmedia.com.

© Copyright 2012 XPmedia.com, Inc. All Rights Reserved Worldwide.
